//timer
/*let sec = 15;
let time = setInterval(myTimer, 1000);
function myTimer() {
    document.getElementById('timer').innerHTML = sec + "sec left";
    sec--;
    if (sec == -1) {
        clearInterval(time);
        alert("Time out!! :(");
    }
}*/



const questions = [
    {
    question: "1. Which of the following languages is more suited to a structured program?",
    answers: {
        a: "PL/1",
        b: "FORTRAN",
        c: "BASIC",
        d: "PASCAL"
    },
    correct: "d"
},
{
    question: "2.Which of the following is the 1's complement of 10?",
    answers: {
        a: "01",
        b: "110",
        c: "11",
        d: "10"
    },
    correct: "a"
},
{
    question: "3.The brain of any computer system is",
    answers: {
        a: "ALU",
        b: "Memory",
        c: "CPU",
        d: "None of The Above"
    },
    correct: "c"
},
{
    question: "4.Which part interprets program instructions and initiate control operations.",
    answers: {
        a: "Input",
        b: "Storage Unit",
        c: "Logic Unit",
        d: "Control Unit"
    },
    correct: "d"
},
{
    question: "5.The binary system uses powers of",
    answers: {
        a: "2",
        b: "10",
        c: "8",
        d: "16"
    },
    correct: "a"
}/*,
{
    question: "6. A computer program that converts assembly language to machine language is",
    answers: {
        a: "Compiler",
        b: "Interpreter",
        c: "Assembler",
        d: "None of The Above"
    },
    correct: "c"
},
{
    question: "7.You can use C++ as a procedural, as well as an object-oriented, language",
    answers: {
        a: "True",
        b: "False",
    },
    correct: "a"
},
{
    question: "8. Which of the following type of class allows only one object of it to be created?",
    answers: {
        a: "Virtual Class",
        b: "Abstract Class",
        c: "Singleton Class",
        d: "Friend Class"
    },
    correct: "c"
},
{
    question: "9. Which of the following is not a type of constructor?",
    answers: {
        a: "Copy Constructor",
        b: "Friend Constructor",
        c: "Default Constructor",
        d: "Parameterized Constructor"
    },
    correct: "b"
},
{
    question: "10. Which of the following concepts means wrapping up of data and functions together?",
    answers: {
        a: "Abstraction",
        b: "Encapsulation",
        c: "Inheritance",
        d: "Polymorphism"
    },
    correct: "b"
}*/
];
